AGORO, BABATUNDE JAMIU

Home Address: No 1, Sadiku Street Off Ekoro Road Abule-Egba Lagos State

Email: babatundeagoro17@gmail.com | babatunde.agoro@yahoo.com

Phone Numbers: 08057711555, 07034390558

PROFILE SUMMARY

A confident and proactive Personnel Psychologist with Guidance and Counselling Educational background, an innovative and creative individual looking forward in making a significant contribution to an esteemed organization while maintaining a working relationship with diverse departments within an organization and extracting ways and methods to develop processes that are more efficient to the growth of organization. Provide and able to address a high volume of customer and management projects with exceptional psychological knowledge and experience in implementing organizational and personnel management for the profitable growth of the organization.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of Birth: 23rd October, 1987

State of Origin: Oyo State

Local Govt. Area Ibadan South East

Nationality: Nigerian Sex: Male Marital Status: Single

SKILLS

- Knowledge of computer software, such as Power point, MS Word, and basic Excel
- Experience with data management system and accurate data entry.
- Good knowledge of creating interpersonal relationship within work environment.
- Excellent problem solving abilities with Psychological techniques and result oriented.
- Ability to solve problems using communication skill, social skill, creative skill and analytical skill
- ❖ Ability to work without or with little supervision

CERTIFICATIONS

Level I, II & III

•	Chartered Institute of Customer Relationship Management. (CICRM)	(2016)
	Associate Member	
•	Chartered Institute of Customer Relationship Management	(2016)
	Post-Graduate Diploma (PGD)	
•	Human Safety Security and Environment (HSE)	(2016)

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Olabisi Onabanjo University Ago-Iwoye, Ogun State (2019)

Master of Personnel Psychology

Olabisi Onabanjo University Ago-Iwoye, Ogun State. (2014)

B.Ed Guidance and Counselling

Olabisi Onabanjo University Ago-Iwoye, Ogun State. (2007)

Information Science and Library Study. (Diploma)

Methodist Secondary Grammar School Elekuro, Ibadan, Oyo State. (2004)

Secondary School Certificate. (SSCE)

Wesley College Practicing School, Elekuro, Ibadan, Oyo State. (1998)

First School Leaving Certificate. (FSLC)

WORK EXPERIENCENCE

Ranbaxy Nigeria Limited Isolo, Lagos State. (Apr 2021 - Till Date)

Administrative Officer
Job Responsibilities:

- > Recording of expenses book used by the marketers to deliver the product on the field.
- > Handled all administrative duties as may be directed by the Managing Director
- > Recording of all payable cheque and utility bills for future references.
- Checking of all delivery goods by the vendors to confirm the number and the quality of the goods.
- > Keeping and recording of vouchers used by every personnel within an organization.
- > Attending to the marketers to provide all equipment using on the field to them.
- > Recording of sponsorship request from people and the amount approved to them.
- \succ Attending to the logistic agencies to received and send packages up countries.
- Recording the details of CME proposed by the marketers to present at their respective point of sales.

Phillipson Global Resources Ogba, Lagos State.

(Jun 2020 - Feb 2021)

HR/Admin

Job Responsibilities:

- Analyze weekly report and the activities to be carried out produce for the client.
- Recording of invoice used to deliver the product to the client.
- Preparing the work plan on the power point to carried out on the site according the approved proposal.

- Recording of all payable utility bills for future references.
- Coordinating and supervising the office assistance in charge of cleaning all the offices and the environment.
- Keeping and recording of vouchers used by every personnel within an organization.
- Compiling all the task to be carried out in order to meet up with client demanding and the delivery date.
- > Ensure the workers welfarism are in good condition.
- > Handled incoming calls and mails from customers and visitors while responding to inquiries and resolving issues.
- > Responding to the issues and complains by the staff and provide a possible solution

Omotosho Power Generation Company Ore, Ondo State.

(Jan 2018 - Nov 2019)

HR Officer/Internship
Job Responsibilities:

- Maintained accurate and up-to-date records of employee training and education compliance to ensure a shared knowledge base throughout the company.
- Maintained accurate and up-to-date records of total number of employee in an organization.
- Ensuring the maintenance of company vehicles to make all vehicles are working perfectly and report to the HRM.
- Maintained accurate interpersonal relationship within workers in an organization.
- Scheduled interviews/training and confirm appointments on behalf of the HR manager to the visitors and applicant.
- Drafted memos and letters and deliver such document to respective departments.
- > Maintained and organized all records documented and other files associate with human resources department.
- Assisting the HRM in attending to the government agencies such as revenue agency, police, custom officer for proper document of the foreign workers and maximum security within an organization.
- > Providing the training manual and other needed for training at accurate time such as projector, amplifier and conducive environment.

Pomat Peters Nig. Ltd. Abule-Egba, Lagos Quality Control Responsibilities:

(Mar 2015 - Nov 2017)

- Conducted routine and non-routine analyses of in-process materials and finished goods to ensure compliance with standards and specifications of the company.
- > Assisted in quality assurance monitoring of finished product to ensure product conformity.
- Carried out analyses on packaging materials such as printed flex, Rollup banner cartons to determine it specifications.
- Ensure the proper sharpness and the graphics on the printing meet-up with the standard

production.

HOBBIES

Listening to music, traveling and connecting with people

REFEREES

Available on request